Anita Weschler Papers
Anita Weschler Papers
- Photographs
  - Album, Hulda Eve Mayer, circa 1900s (Box 71)
  - Album, 1915 (Oversize 9)
  - Album, 1918-1919 (Box 71)
  - Album, Europe, 1922 (Box 71)
  - Album, children, undated (Box 72)
  - Album, Florida real estate, undated (Box 72)
  - Album, Montreal, undated (Box 72)
  - Album, portraits, undated (Box 72)
  - Album, Thousand Islands, Niagara Falls, undated (Box 72)
- Printed material
  - Exhibitions (Box 72)
  - Periodicals, 3 folders (Box 73)
  - Periodicals (Oversize 4)
  - Playbill, 3 folders (Box 73)
  - Programs (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 74)
- Recordings
  See also Artwork: Sculpture: Cassette and slides, George and Gladys Robinson.
  - Anita Weschler No. 1, Parts 3 and 4, 01/10/1979; weschler_a_005; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Anita Weschler No. 2, 01/17/1979; weschler_a_007; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Anita Weschler No. 3, 01/22/1979; weschler_a_008; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Anita Weschler No. 3 (MacDowell Colony, Part 3) and No. 4 (MacDowell Colony, Part 2), 01/28/1979; weschler_a_009; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Anita Weschler, No. 10, 10/13/1980; weschler_a_013; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Anita Weschler: Reminiscences, 01/10/1979; weschler_a_006; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 53)
  - Interviews: Manila Barber, 08/04/1978; weschler_a_003; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Katherine Price; Charles Stover, 06/30/1978; weschler_a_002; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Lenox Quartet at Waverly Place: Bartok and Dvorak, 12/16/1978; weschler_a_004; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Longhill, No. 8, 1952; 1953; weschler_a_001; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - Mediators, The, No. 7, 02/11/1979; weschler_a_012; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - War Years, No. 6, Part 1, 02/06/1979; weschler_a_010; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
  - War Years, No. 6, Parts 2 and 3, 02/06/1979; weschler_a_011; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 84)
- Writings
  - Articles
    - Art and the Mirror, typescript (Box 75)
    - Artist and Angel, draft A, typescript revised; draft B typescript revised; draft C, typescript carbon (Box 75)
    - Belle Boas: An Appreciation and Recollection, 1954; draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript carbon; correspondence (Box 75)
    - Bright Angel and Artist, typescript carbon (Box 75)
    - The Case For Clay, draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript revised and typescript notes (Box 75)
    - A Defense of Modern Art, draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript carbon (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - The Drama of Childhood, autobiographical, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - Introduction to Aesthetics, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - Modern Art Has Many Faces, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - Modern Art: Root Flower and Fruit, draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript carbon revised; draft C, typescript revised; draft D, typescript carbon (Box 75)
    - On the Sale of American Art, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - On Sculpture and Architecture, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - Reminiscence of Rainier, typescript (Box 75)
    - Sculpture in the Home, typescript revised (Box 75)
    - Wisely Not Too Well, 1954; draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript carbon (Box 75)
  - Book reviews
    - A Harvest of Hebrew Verse, Harry H. Fein, 1934; typescript revised (Box 75)
  - Books
    - Novel, untitled, typescript carbon, pp 1-51, Draft A, typescript revised; Draft B, typescript carbon, including notes and outline (Box 75)
  - Books, verse
    - The Loom circa, 1954; typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 75)
    - Nightshade
      - Drafts, 1930; draft A, holograph and typescript; draft B, typescript and typescript carbon revised, including agreement with publisher; draft C, typescript carbon revised; 3 folders (Box 75)
      - Drafts, draft D, typescript carbon (Box 76)
      - Galley proof (Box 76)
      - Published edition, Colony Press, New York, 1931; Sent to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - The Tightrope Walker
      - Drafts, draft A, typescript; draft B, typescript carbon; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Notebook, 3 typescript copies, partially revised (Box 76)
      - Poems eliminated, typescript carbons (Box 76)
  - Diaries
    - [Volume 1, Europe], 1922 (Box 76)
    - [Volume 2], 1934 (Box 76)
    - [Volume 3], 1940-1942 (Box 76)
    - [Volume 4], 1941 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 5], 1941-1944; 2 volumes (Box 77)
    - [Volume 6], 1946 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 7], 1947; 1954 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 8], 1950; 2 volumes (Box 77)
    - [Volume 9], 1951 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 10], 1952-1953 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 11], 1955 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 12], 1955-1956 (Box 77)
    - [Volume 13], 1956 (Box 78)
    - [Volume 14-15], 1956; 2 volumes (Box 78)
    - [Volume 16], 1953-1956 (Box 78)
    - [Volume 17], 1957-1958 (Box 78)
    - [Untitled], 1975 (Box 78)
    - [Volume 18], Undated (Box 78)
  - Essays
    - Of Science, Humanism and F.C.S. Schiller Apr, 1956; typescript carbon (Box 78)
  - Lectures and talks (Box 78)
  - Letters to the editor (Box 78)
  - Notebooks
    - Chores, memos, 2 volumes (Box 78)
    - School (Box 79)
    - School, costume design (Box 79)
    - Typescript fragments, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Notes
    - Re: Art, 1954; undated; holograph, typescript (Box 79)
    - Art course, holograph (Box 80)
    - Re: Artists, holograph, typescript (Box 80)
    - Re: Design, holograph (Box 80)
    - For book on sculpture, 1940; typescript (Box 80)
    - French course, typescript (Box 80)
    - Re: Interior decorating, 1936-1948; typescript revised (Box 80)
    - Re: Lectures of others, 1939; holograph (Box 80)
    - Re: Painting and paintings, holograph, typescript (Box 80)
    - Plans, reminders, schedules, holograph, typescript (Box 80)
    - Re: Sculptor's Guild, 1942; holograph (Box 80)
    - Re: Sculpture
      - Human Events Series, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 80)
      - The Humanist, typescript carbon (Box 81)
      - For Sculptor's Guild (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-1957; holograph, typescript (Box 81)
    - Re: Teaching, typescript (Box 81)
    - Re: Techniques, holograph, typescript (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Plays
    - Untitled, typescript revised (Box 81)
    - Fragments, typescript (Box 81)
  - Poems
    - Lists of, holograph, typescript (Box 81)
    - Early, from school publications, 1918-1922; holograph, typescript carbon, printed material (Box 81)
    - First drafts, published and unpublished, 1922-1925; holograph (Box 81)
    - [General], 1924-1929; holograph, typescript (Box 81)
    - A-D, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 81)
    - E-I, 1927-1956; typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 82)
    - J-R, 1931; holograph, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 82)
    - S-Y, 1921; holograph, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 82)
    - Notebooks, 1929; 1930,; 1932; 3 volumes (Box 82)
    - Notebooks, 1932 (Box 83)
  - Press releases, holograph, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 83)
  - Radio interview, typescript and typescript carbon revised (Box 83)
  - Radio talks, 1938; typescript (Box 83)
  - Recipe, Greenwich Village Gourmet, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Short stories
    - High Diver, typescript (Box 83)
    - The King of the Thousand Islands, typescript revised (Box 83)
    - Summer Crossing, holograph (Box 83)
  - Untitled short pieces
    - Autobiographical pieces, 1938 (Box 83)
    - Re: Weschler exhibits
      - Human Events, draft A, typescript revised; draft B, typescript revised (Box 83)
      - for Pennsylvania Railroad, 1934; holograph, typescript carbon revised (Box 83)
      - Sculptor's Holiday, typescript revised, typescript carbon (Box 83)
      - Travelling show (Box 83)
    - Re: Exhibits of other artists, 1933-1934; holograph, typescript (Box 83)
    - Re: Other artists, 1958; typescript carbon (Box 83)
    - Re: Play Sculpture competition design, 1954; typescript (Box 83)
  - Writings of others
    - Carmer, Carl, Is There an American Culture, typescript reproduction (Box 83)
    - Channin, Richard, Three Stages of the Copernican Revolution in Science and Art, Apr 22, 1970 (Box 83)
    - Hudnut, Joseph
      - The Architecture of the Yard, Harvard Alumni Bulletin, Mar 30, 1946 (Box 83)
      - Architecture's Place in City Planning, Architectural Record, reprint (Box 83)
      - The Art in Housing, Tomorrow, See Correspondence [General], Oct 25, 1943.
      - The Art and Science of City Planning, Michigan Society of Architects, Weekly Bulletin, Apr 10 1945 (Box 83)
      - Blueprint for a University, 1944; reprint (Box 83)
      - City Planning and the Public Mind, Architectural Record, reprint (Box 83)
      - The Crow Island School, See Correspondence [General], Jul 11, 1941.
      - The Kleinhans Music Hall, See Correspondence [General], Jul 1, 1941.
      - Patchwork Planning, See Correspondence [General], Jul 29, 1944.
      - Picture, Sentiment and Symbol, typescript carbon (Box 83)
      - The Political Art of Planning, See Correspondence [General], Nov 23, 1943.
      - The Post Modern House, inscribed by author, reprint, Architectural Record, May 1945; reprint (Box 83)
      - Ultimus Romanorum, See Correspondence [General], Mar 4, 1941.
      - What is This City Planning?, See Correspondence [General], Nov 4, 1944.
    - Lamprey, Louise, 1923; play, short stories, poems, article, typescript and typescript carbon (Box 83)
    - Weschler, J. Charles, Blue Eye plays, typescript carbon (Box 83)
    - Fragment, unidentified (Box 83)
Partial index to correspondence
The majority of correspondence is incoming (to Anita Weschler). Outgoing letters (from Weschler) are denoted with an asterisk (*). "PM" indicates that the date was taken from a postmark on the envelope rather than from the letter itself.
Please note that this index is NOT comprehensive. It covers only the [General] correspondence in Boxes 22-34. It does not include Business or Personal correspondence (Boxes 8-22).
Allen, Mary C. Mar 9 [1941 PM]
Aluminum Company of America *Aug 9, 1946 Sep 25, 1946 *Oct 8, 1946 Nov 12, 1946
American Artists Group Jun 18, 1938 Dec 30, 1940 Jan 11, 1941 Feb 7, 1941 Oct 10, 1945
American Federation of Arts and American Art Annual Nov 26, 1934 *Jan 6, 1938 *Aug 11, 1938 *Sep 8, 1938 *Sep 19, 1938 *Oct 28, 1938 *Nov 2, 1938 Nov 4, 1938 *Nov 5, 1938 *Nov 14, 1938 *Nov 14, 1938 *Nov 22, 1938 Nov 29, 1938 *Dec 1, 1938 Dec 5, 1938 *Dec 8, 1938 Dec 12, 1938 Dec 15, 1938 *Dec 16, 1938 *Dec 16, 1938 *Jan 6, 1939 Jan 23, 1939 *Aug 17, 1939 Nov 5, 1940 Dec 17, 1940 Feb 26, 1941 Jan 26, 1945 Feb 16, 1945 Jun 8, 1945 May 14, 1947 Jun 12, 1947 Jul 6, 1951 Feb 14, 1952 [Jun 5, 1952 PM] Mar 22, 1960 n.d.
American Jewish Committee Feb 1, 1951
American Museum of Natural History *Oct 27, 1950 Oct 31, 1950 *Feb 15, 1951 *Feb 15, 1951
Antin, Mary (1881-1949) Feb 15, 1937 Mar 9, 1937
Architectural League of New York Feb 1, 1936 Jan 23, 1951 Oct 1, 1951 Feb 10, 1954 Jan 31, 1955 Feb 3, 1955 Feb 28, 1955 Oct 7, 1957
Arms, C. Louise Feb 11, 1937
Armstrong, Susannah [Mar 1937]
Art Association of New Orleans Feb 4, 1936
Art Association of Newport Jun 28, 1944 Jul 11, 1944
Art Institute of Chicago Sep 26, 1938 Jan 8, 1951
Art Students League of New York Feb 4, 1935 Mar 10, 1947 Dec 27, 1949 Jul 29, 1952 Oct 13, 1952 Apr 17, 1954 Feb 4, 1957 Feb 26, 1957 Jun 26, 1957 Aug 29, 1957 Nov 12, 1957 May 5, 1958
Artists Equity Association [circa 19381 Feb 7, 1952 Nov 24, 1952 Dec 3, 1953 Dec 10, 1953 *Dec 15, 1953 *Oct 22, 1954
Baker, Olin J. Sep 18, 1957 Sep 26, 1957 [Oct 9, 1957 PM] Oct 8, 1958
Ball, Laurance A. Jul 24, 1923 Jul 21, 1925 Nov 11, 1930 Feb 15, 1931 May 29, 1931 Aug 10, 1932
Barlow, Howard (1892- ) Feb 17, 1937
Bartholemew, Zelina Feb 3, 1937
Bates, Sylvia Chatfield Feb 19, 1937
Bauer, Marion (1887-1955) Oct 12, 1939
Beach, Amy M. (1867-1944) Feb 4, 1937
Benet, William Rose (1886-1950) Jan 15, 1935 Jun 11, 1936 Aug 13, 1936 Feb 8, 1937 Jun 17, 1943 *May 19, 1943 n.d.
Berkowitz, Leon L. [Jan 21, 1937 PM]
Beston Henry (1888- ) [Feb 1937]
Bianco, Pamela (1906- ) Dec 23, 1936
Black, John Feb 3, 1937
Blum, Helaine D. Sep 10, 1940 Sep 17, 1941 [Sep 25, 1941 PM] Nov 14, 1941 Jan 3, 1942 Jan 28, 1942
Boswell, Edna [Dec 7, 1949 PM]
Boswell, Peyton Jr. (1904-1950) Jul 7, 1926 Nov 24, 1942 Mar 1, 1943 [Feb 2, 1944 PM] May 27, 1946 May 19, 1947 May 20, 1948 Jun 28, 1948 [Aug 5, 1948 PM]
Botkin Henry (1896- ) *[Jan 13, 1958]
Brian, Doris Apr 11, 1937 [Jun 30, 1940 PM] [Aug 5, 1940 PM] [Aug 15, 1940 PM] [Aug 20, 1940 PM] [Oct 14, 1940 PM] Jun 24, [1941 PM] Jul 14, 1941 [Jul 22, 1941 PM] [Aug 8, 1941 PM] *Mar 6, 1942 *[Jun 13, 1942 PM] Oct 31, 1943 May 27 [1944 PM] [Oct 11, 1944 PM] [Oct 18, 1944 PM] [Nov 18, 1944 PM] Mar 27, 1946 [Jun 25, 1946 PM] [Oct 16, 1946 PM] [1946 PM] *[circa 1953] [Jan 14, 1954 PM] Dec 8, 1954 n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d.
Briggs Manufacturing Company *[ca Feb 15, 1946] Feb 20, 1946 *Feb 26, 1946 *Mar 15, 1946 *Mar 19, 1946 *Apr 18, 1946
Brinser, H. L. Admiral (1876- ) *May 21, 1943 May 22, 1943
Brooklyn Museum Jan 2, 1934 Dec 30, 1937 Aug 1, 1938 Sep 12, 1938 Jan 8, 1951
Bruce, Edward (1879- ) Oct 21, 1938 *Oct 24, 1938
Buchholz Gallery *Apr 24, 1946 May 2, 1946 May 18, 1946
Bufano, Florence Aug 21, 1935 Dec 27, 1937 Aug 27,[ca, 1941] Nov 15, 1946 Dec 15, 1948
Byerly, Blanche A. Feb 10, 1936
Caesar Doris (1892- ) circa [1950]
Calhoun, Carolyn Jul 16, 1949 Aug 10, 1949 Sep 6, 1949 Sep 8, 1949 Sep 12 [1949 PM]
Canby, Marion Gause (1885- ) Jan 30, 1937 Dec 27, 1937 *Oct 9, 1939 *Oct 23, 1939
Carl Byoir and Associates, Inc. Jul 25, 1956 Aug 6, 1956 *[circa Aug 8, 1956] Aug 29, 1956 *[circa Aug 30, 1956] Oct 15, 1956
Carmer Betty [Nov 24, 1946 PM]
Carnegie Institute, Department of Fine Arts Sep 4, 1940 Dec 10, 1940 *Dec 17, 1940 Dec 19, 1940 Feb 4, 1941 Feb 7, 1941 Feb 22, 1941 *Feb 25, 1941 Feb 26, 1941 May 28, 1953
Cecere, Gaetaro Feb 1, 1936
Cheney, Sheldon Warren (1886- ) Feb 18, 1937
Child, Philip (1898- ) Dec 19, 1936
Childers, Lemuel J. Dec 19, 1936
Clarke Catherine Caville [Jul 13, 1938 PM] [Aug 14, 1938 PM] [Oct 31, 1938 PM] [circa Nov 1, 1938] [Jul 14, 1939 PM] Aug 2 [1939 PM] [Oct 28, 1939 PM] [1939 PM] Jul 9, 1940 Aug 12 [1940 PM] Sep 8 [1940 PM] Sep 14 [1940 PM] [circa 1940] Jul 17, 1941 [Nov 28, 1941 PM] Dec 23 [1941]
Clay Club Sculpture Center Dec 1, 1948
Cleugh, Sophia Feb 17, 1937
Cohen, Morris A. (1892- ) Feb 15, 1937
Cole, Arthur F. *Oct 15, 1941 Oct 17, 1941
Coleman, Laurence Vail (1893- ) Feb 3, 1937
Colin, Ralph F. Dec 8, 1930 Dec 12, 1930
College Art Association Apr 5, 1936
Colum, Padraic (1881- ) Aug 15, 1934 Feb 5, 1935 Mar 29, 1935 Jul 5, 1935 Jul 30, 1935
Columbia Museum of Art May 28, 1953 *Jun 3, 1953 Jul 11, 1953 *Jul 15, 1953 *Oct 2, 1953 Oct 6, 1953 *Oct 8, 1953 Oct 9, 1953 *[circa Oct 10, 1953] Oct 10, 1953 *[Oct 14, 1953] Oct 29, 1953 Nov 10, 1953 Nov 24, 1953 *Dec 2, 1953 *Dec 9, 1953 *[ca 1953] Jan 4, 1954 Feb 20, 1957
Common Council for American Unity May 17, 1944 Mar 1, 1945
Constantine, Mildred Feb 26, 1953 [circa 1953]
Contemporary Arts Association Jul 9, 1953 Sep 22, 1953 Oct 16, 1953 *Jan 28, 1954 (?)
Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art Jun 19, 1957
Copland, Aaron 1900- ) [Feb 1937] May 5, 1952
Coward-McCann, Inc. *Oct 5, 1945 [Oct 7 (?) 1945] Oct 11, 1945 *Oct ? 1945
Creative Age Press, Inc. Jan 7, 1946 Mar 1, 1946
Cromwell Publications Apr 21, 1939
Crownfield, Gertrude Frederica (1867-1945) [Feb. 1937]
Cue May 2, 1941
Cuming, Robert Feb 3, [1939] Mar 6, [1939 PM]
Currier Gallery of Art [circa 1938 ]
Cuthbert, Clifton (1907- ) [May 30, 1935 PM [May 31, 1935 PM] [Jun 1, 1935 PM] [Jun 7, 1935 PM] [Jun 25, 1935 PM] Jul 22, [ca 1935] [Aug 9, 1935 PM] [Aug 17, 1935 PM] [Sep 16, 1935 PM] [Oct 22, 1935 PM] [Dec 4, 1935 PM] [Jun 24, 1936 PM] [Jul 3, 1936 PM] Jul 9, 1936 [Jul ? 1936 PM] [Aug 17, 1936 PM] [Jun 13, 1937 PM) [Jul 29, 1937 PM]
Daniels, Lewis C. Jan 29, 1937
Davidson, A. Wolfe Feb 16, 1956
DeCasseres, David *Aug 9, 1949
Dent, Adolphe May 28, 1936
Diamond, David (1915- ) Feb 17, 1937 [Dec 6, 1952 PM]
Dodd, Mead and Company Nov 21, 1945
Draper, Ruth (1884-1956) [Feb 1, 1937 PM]
Dryfoos, Nancy Proskauer [Mar 31, 1952 PM] [Jan 7, 1953 PM] [Feb 22, 1953 PM]
Duveen, Albert Apr 28, 1956
Dworkin, Robert [May 1, 1954 PM]
Eaves, Winslow (1922- ) Apr 1 1, 1950
Ehrlich, Leonard (1905- ) [circa 1936] [Feb 18, 1937 PM] *Apr 9, 1937 Apr 21, 1937 [Jan 4, 1939 PM]
Emerson, Sybil (1895- ) [1936]
Farmer, L.M., Mrs. Oct 5, 1933
Federation of Modern Painters and Sculptors, Inc. Jan 6, 1941 Feb 26, 1944 Sep 29, 1944 Sep 26, 1945 *Sep 28, 1945 *Oct 1, 1945 May 20, 1946 *Oct 2, 1946 [circa 1946]
Ferguson, Duncan Nov 27, 1940 Dec 10, 1940
Fillmore, Parker Hoystead (1878-1944) Feb 6, 1936 Feb 6, 1937 Feb 19, 1937 Mar 8, 1937
Finch Junior College Apr 26, 1949
Fineman, Irving (1893- ) [Feb 1937]
Flack, Marjorie (1897-1958) Feb 9, 1937
Florence Museum Sep 26, 1953 *Oct 15, 1953 Oct 22, 1953 [circa Oct 1953] Dec 6, 1953 Dec 31, 1953
Ford Foundation Jul 23, 1958 Jun 4, 1959
Fortune Apr 30, 1937
Franklin, Fabian (1853-1939) Apr 13, 1931
Freakford Trust Company Feb 4, 1944 Mar 3, 1944 Apr 13, 1944 *Apr 13, 1944
Freydberg, Ralph M. [Jan 29, 1922] May 14, 1922 May 14, 1922 Jun 14, 1922 Jun 26, 1922 Jul 18, [1922] Jul 24, 1922 Aug 21, [1922 PM] Aug 21, 1922 Sep 21, [1922 PM] Sep 21, 1922 [Sep 22, 1922 PM] [Oct 7, 1922 PM] [Oct 20, 1922 PM] [Oct 23, 1922 PM) Oct 24, 1922 [Oct 29 PM, circa 1922] [Nov 2, 1922 PM] Nov 22, 1922 [circa 1922] [Jan 9, 1923 PM] [Feb 13, 1923 PM] [Feb 19, 1923 PM] [Feb 24, 1923 PM] [May 4, 1923 PM] [Jun 13, PM, circa 1923] [Jul 1, 1923 PM] [Jul 3, 1923 PM] [Jul 7, 1923 PM] [Jul 12, 1923 PM] [Jul 13, 1923 PM] Jul 19, 1923 [Jul 20, 1923 PM] [Jul 25, 1923 PM] [Jul 27, 1923 PM] [Aug 6, 1923 PM] [Aug 13, 1923 PM] [Aug 27, 1923 PM] [Sep 25, 1923 PM] Apr 18, [circa 1924] [May 28, 1924 PM] [May 31, 1924 PM] [Jun 4, 1924 PM] [Jun 9, 1924 PM] [Jun 26, 1924 PM] [Jun 28, 1924 PM] Jun 28, [circa 1924] Jul 2, [1924 PM] Jul 7, 1924 [Jul 11, 1924 PM] [Jul 18, 1924 PM] [Jul 19, 1924 PM] [Jul 25, 1924 PM] [Aug 1, 1924 PM] [Aug 10, 1924 PM] [Aug 25, 1924 PM] [Nov 24, 1924 PM] Dec 5, [circa 1924] [Dec 9, 1924 PM] [circa 1924] [Jan 9, 1925 PM] [Feb 2, 1925 PM] [Feb 14, 1925 PM] [Apr 2, 1925 PM] Aug 2, 1925 [Mar 5, 1926] [Jul 25, 1926 PM] [Aug 17, 1926 PM] [Dec 5, 1926 PM] [Dec 22, 1926 PM] [Jun 14, 1927 PM] [Jul 10, 1928 PM] Oct 26, [1931 PM] [Oct 26, 1934 PM] Dec 10, 1934 Oct 20, [1937 PM] Dec 14, [1937] [Mar 28, 1938 PM] [May 27, 1938 PM] [Oct 25, 1938 PM] [Dec 9, 1938 PM] [Jan 16, 1939 PM]
Friends of American Art Jan 31, 1940
Frost, Frances (1905-1959) Jul 16, 1922 Aug 22, [1934 PM] Nov 6, 1934 Dec 1, [1934 PM] Jan 24, [1935 PM] [Mar 23, 1935 PM] Apr 16, 1935 [May 3, 1935 PM] [May 11, 1935 PM] [Jun 1, 1935 PM] [Jun 6, 1935 PM] [Jul 3, 1935 PM] [Jul 26, 1935 PM] [Oct 17, 1935 PM] [Oct 29, 1935 PM] [Nov 2, 1935 PM] [Nov 19, 1935 PM] [Nov 26, 1935 PM] [Nov 29, 1935 PM] [Dec 9, 1935 PM] [Dec 24, 1935] [Jan 3, 1936 PM] [Jan 9, 1936 PM] Jan 16, [1936 PM] [Jan 20, 1936 PM] [Jan 26, 1936 PM] [Feb 11, 1936 PM] [Feb 15, 1936 PM] [Feb 20, 1936 PM] Feb 26, 1936 Mar 19, [1936 PM] Mar 30, [1936 PM] Apr 16, [1936 PM] Apr 20, [1936 PM] May 19, [1936 PM] Jul 23, 1936 Jul 24, [1936] Aug 13, 1936 Aug 25, [1936 PM] [Oct 1936 PM] [Nov 22, 1936 PM] Dec 11, [1936 PM] Dec 30, [1936] [Jan 26, [1937 PM] Feb 15 [1937 PM] [Mar 13 [1937 PM] Mar 24, [1937 PM] Apr 10, [1937 PM] [Apr 19, 1937 PM] May 19, [1937 PM] Jun 17, [1937 PM] [Jun 21, 1937 PM] Jul 3, [1937] Sep 20, [1937 PM] Oct 14, [1937 PM] Nov 8, [1937 PM] Dec 15, [1937] Dec 21, [1937] Dec 23, [1937 PM] [Dec 27, 1937] [circa 1937] [Mar 28, 1938 PM] Apr 27, [1938 PM] [Oct 31, 1938 PM] [Jun 29, 1939 PM] Aug 2, [1939 PM] Nov 26, 1940 Feb 26, 1941 Mar 26, 1941 Apr 30, 1941 Aug 12, 1941 Mar 9, 1942 May 1, 1942 May 20, 1942 Aug 28, 1942 [Nov 5, 1943 PM] Jan 23, [1944 PM] Mar 18, [1944] [May 7, 1946 PM] Jul 9, 1946 Jun 18, [1948 PM] Dec 8, [1948 PM] May 7, 1952 [circa 1952] Oct 8, [1952 PM] Oct 6, 1954 Jan 8, 1955 Mar 4, 1955 Aug 4, [1955 PM] n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d.
Fruhauf, A. [Jul 22 PM] [circa 1932]
Gallimore, L.B. *Nov 12, 1938 Nov 15, 1938
Glowacki, Michaline [circa 1926] [Feb PM] 24 [1948 PM] [Mar PM] 25 [1948 PM] [Oct PM] 18 [1948 PM] Nov 7, 1948 Jan 4, 1949 Jun 1, 1949 Jun 17 [1949 PM] [Jun PM] 24 [1949 PM] [Jul 1, 1949 PM] Jul 28, [1949 PM] [Sep 28, 1949 PM] [Apr PM1 25 [1950 PM] May 2, [1950 PM] Jul 11, [1950] [Aug 12, 1950 PM] [Oct 24, 1950 PM] [Nov 1950 PM] [Nov PM] 14 [1950 PM] Jan 3, 1951 [circa Mar 17, 1951 PM] [May 62 1951 PM] Aug 7 11951 PM] [Aug 22 1951 PM] Nov 24 L1951 PM] [1951 PM] [circa 1951] Jun 1, [circa 1952] Jun 6, [1952 PM] [Aug 6, 1952 PM] [Aug 6 1952 PM] Sep 1, [1952 PM] Oct 4, [1952 PM] Dec 1, [1952 PM] Dec 2, 1952 [Dec 8, 1952 PM] [1952 PM] [Feb 11, 1953 PM] [Jun PM] 23 [1953 PM] [Dec 18, 1953 PM] [Sep 17, 1954 PM] [Nov PM] 12 [1954 PM] [1954 PM] [1954] May 9, 1956 Aug 30, 1956 [1957 PM] n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d.
Golden, Trudy Apr 3, 1944 [Jul 24, 1944 PM] [Jul 25, 1944 PM] [Aug 17, 1944 PM] Oct 12, 1944 Nov 3, 1944 Nov 30, 1944 Dec 5, 1944 Jan 4, 1945 Jan 29, 1945 Mar 7, 1945 May 4, 1945 Jun 14, 1945 Jun 20, 1945 Jul 2, 1945 Sep 5, 1945 Sep 8, 1945 Sep 28, 1945 Nov 11, 1945 Nov 19, 1945 Dec 9, 1945 Dec 20, 1945 Apr 9, 1948 [Jul 8, 1949 PM] [Aug 13, 1952 PM]
Gorelik, Frances Mar 22, 1942 [Jan 5, 1943 PM] Apr 18, 1943 Aug 26, 1943 Aug 28, 1943 Jun 6, 1945 May 24, 1946 Aug 1, 1946 Sep 28, 1946 Nov 1 1, 1946 Nov 15, 1946 Dec 17, 1946 Oct 16, 1947 Nov 24, 1947 Aug 15, 1949 Feb 13 [1953 PM] [Feb 17, 1953 PM] Nov 13, 1954 Feb 29, 1955 Jul 26 1955 Mar [?] 1956 Nov 3, 1956 Aug 12, 1957 Nov 4, 1957 n.d.
Gorelik, Mordecai Jan 4, 1947 Aug 18, 1948 Feb 10, 1949 [circa 1949] [circa 1950] [circa 1950]
Gorham Company Oct 17, 1946
Gottshalk, Amiee Feb 13, 1937
Grand Central Art Galleries Jun 20, 1949 *Jun 29, 1949
Graham, French W. *Jul 21, 1938 Jul 30, 1938 *Oct 24, 1938 Oct 26, 1938 *Nov 7, 1938 Nov 9, 1938 *Jan 23, 1939 Jan 24, 1939 *Jan 30, 1939 Feb 6, 1939 *Feb 9, 1939 Mar 27, 1947 Mar 29, 1947 [circa 1947]
Grandin, Ruth L.T. Nov 5, 1938 Dec 5 [1938 PM] Feb 21 [1939 PM] [May 26, 1939 PM] Nov 26 [1939 PM] Sep 21, 1940 Oct 26 [1940 PM] Dec 10 [1940 PM] [Feb 7, 1941 PM] Feb 14, 1941 Mar 14 [1941 PM] Apr 10 [1941 PM] May 19 [1941 PM] Jun 27 [1941 PM] Jul 2 [1941 PM] Jul 21 [1941 PM] [Jul 31, 1941 PM] Sep 2 [1941 PM] [Sep 29, 1942 PM] Jun 22 [1943 PM]
Greenbaum, Beatrice [Aug 30, 1929 PM] Mar 25, 1930 PM] [Nov 12, 1932 PM] [Apr 19, 1933 PM] [Aug 2 1934 PM] Jun 9 [1937 PM] [Nov 18, 1940 PM] May 16 [1945] [Nov 29, 1956 PM] [Jun 25, 1957 PM]
Griffis, Elliot (1893- ) Mar 3, 1935 Mar 28, 1935
Gross, Chaim (1904- ) [circa 1939] Feb 28, 1940
Guade, Richard Sep 8, 1949 Aug 12, 1953 Jun 9, 1955 Jul 11 [1955] [Dec 9, 1955 PM] [1956 PM] Dec 16, 1956
Guerrero, Mary [Feb 2, 1948 PM] [Jan 19, 1949 PM] Feb 9, 1952 Feb 11, 1955
Guglulmi, O. Louis Feb 16, 1937
Guild Artists Bureau, Inc. Oct 7, 1941 *Oct 30, 1941
Halpert, Edith Gregor (1899- ) *May 23, 1946 May 24, 1946 *Jun 11, 1946
Heine, Irwin Millard Jan 27, 1939 Apr 6, 1939 [May 24, 1939 PM] Jul 8, 1939 Jan 23, 1940 Dec 27, 1944 Jan 12, 1945 May 22, 1945 PM] Aug 23, 1946 [Sep 4, 1946 PM] Oct 12, 1946 [May 16, 1947 PM] Jun 6, 1947 Jun 16, 1947 Dec 10, 1948 May 12, 1949 Jan 1, 1950 Dec 14, 1953 Jun 8, 1954 Dec 7, 1954
Heine, Rita Jun 23, 1947 Jun 29, 1947 Sep 29, 1947 [Oct 12, 1953 PM]
Heiner, Lorraine Aug 16, 1948
Hellinger, Joshua (1907-1960) Apr 27, 1933 Oct 2, 1933 Jan 6, 1934 Jun 16, 1934 Jun 19, 1934 Jun 22, 1934 Jul 5, 1934 Jul 22, 1934 Aug 8, 1935 Oct 4, 1937
Henry, Harold (1884-1956) Feb 1937
Heiber, Walter F. Jan 29, 1943
Hier, Ethel Glenn (1889- ) [circa 1937]
High School of Music and Art Mar 5, 1948 *Mar 11, 1948 Mar 19, 1948 *Mar 24 1948 May [?J 1948 May 25, 1948 Apr 26, 1949